snapnzip.com 2014-06-26

# Fashion accessories. Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting snapnzip.com and taking the time to read our Privacy. We take your personal information seriously and don't sell it to anyone. We collect just enough data from you for order fulfillment or marketing efforts.

**Data Collection and Use**

We collect the data you give us:  contact information (name, email address, mailing address, phone number) and preferences information (order history). We might also routinely gather information about your computer such as your IP address. We use this information to analyze traffic to the site in order to improve our website and marketing efforts.

After processing a credit card transaction, we are done with it and do not store the credit card number in our database.

**Cookies**

We may send a small cookie to your computer when you visit our website. This will allow us to track your shopping preferences on our website so we can enhance your future visits to this website.  You can configure your browser to reject cookies but this may hinder your use of certain functionalty of this website.

**Security**

We have implemented security practices and technical measures to protect the personal data that we have under our control from unauthorized access, improper use and disclosure, unauthorized destruction or accidental loss.

If you use PayPal to finalize your order, its privacy statement and security practices will apply to your information. We encourage you to read that privacy statement before providing your information.

**Consent and inquiries**

By continuing to use this site and accessing the information on this website, you signal acceptance of the terms and disclaimer set forth above. If you do not accept any of these terms, leave this website now. If you have any inquiry or concern about our privacy policy or the way in which we are handling personal data please contact [info@snapnzip.com](mailto:info@snapnzip.com). If at any time you wish us to cease processing your information please send a message to [info@snapnzip.com](mailto:info@snapnzip.com).

**Disclaimer**

All brands and their marks indicated on snapnzip.com are trademarks or registered trademarks of said brands, or their subsidiaries (collectively Chloe, Coach, Gucci, Juicy Couture, Marc Jacobs, Kate Spade New York, Michael Kors, Movado, Neiman Marcus, Rebecca Minkoff, Swaroski, Tory Burch, Tumi, Versace) in the United States, Canada and/or other jurisdictions.  All graphics, logos, and service names are the trademarks or trade dress of said brands.
